Finding Aid for Vassar (Mich.) Village Council records, 1871-1948
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Vassar (Mich.) Village Council records 1871-1948
Vassar (Mich.). Village Council.
1 linear foot and 4 oversize volumes
89390 Cc 2; CC Outsize
Minutes of the Village Council of Vassar, Michigan; also indexes to records of the Riverside Cemetery Association.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group came from the Bullard Sanford Public Library in Vassar, Michigan (donor no. 6995 ).
Periodic additions to the records are not expected.
The record group is open to research.
Vassar, Michigan is located in Tuscola County in the thumb region of Michigan.
The record group is arranged into two series: Council Minutes and Other Materials. The Council Minutes are bound volumes of proceedings of the village council. Other materials includes a record of interments and deeds of the Riverside Cemetery Association.
Subjects:
Cemeteries--Michigan--Vassar.; Riverside Cemetery Association (Vassar, Mich.); Tuscola County (Mich.); Vassar (Mich.)
- Council Minutes
  - April 1871-March 1881 (Box 1)
  - March 1881-September 1887 (Volume 1)
  - September 1887-December 1897 (Volume 2)
  - January 1898-March 1907 (Volume 3)
  - March 1907-March 1919 (Volume 4)
  - April 1919-May 1923 (Box 1)
  - June 1923-April 1931 (Box 1)
  - June 1931-March 1941 (Box 1)
  - March 1941-December 1948 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous loose materials from council minute volumes, 1881-1919, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Other materials
  - Oaths of Office, 1904-1931 (Box 1)
  - Riverside Cemetery Association
    - Index of Interments through September 1939 (Box 1)
    - Index to Deeds (Box 1)